export const QUIZ_DATA = [
  {
    question: 'What is 2+7?',
    options: ['3', '7', '9', '11'],
    answer: '9',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is 5x15?',
    options: ['25', '50', '75', '100'],
    answer: '75',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is 6x9?',
    options: ['54', '36', '24', '69'],
    answer: '54',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is 0+0?',
    options: ['0', '1', '100', '1000'],
    answer: '0',
  },
  {
    question: 'How many alphabets are there in the word ‘apple’?',
    options: ['10', '15', '5', '7'],
    answer: '5',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the colour of moon?',
    options: ['red', 'orange', 'pink', 'white'],
    answer: 'white',
  },
  {
    question: 'How many legs does a chicken have?',
    options: ['1', '2', '4', '10'],
    answer: '2',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which one of these is not a programming language?',
    options: ['C', 'C++', 'Javascript', 'English'],
    answer: 'English',
  },
  {
    question: 'How many days are there in a week?',
    options: ['10', '5', '7', '6'],
    answer: '7',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these is not a react library inbuilt hook?',
    options: ['useState', 'useRef', 'useImperativeHandle', 'useLocalStorage'],
    answer: 'useLocalStorage',
  },
];
